看好了 超级酷
Watch this,it's really cool.
呼叫莱纳德.霍夫斯塔德
Call leonard hofstadter.
您需要呼叫海伦.博克斯莱特纳吗?
Did you say: "Call helen boxleitner"?
不
No.
呼叫莱纳德.霍夫斯塔德
Call leonard hofstadter.
您需要呼叫坦布尔.巴斯塞得吗?
Did you say: "Call temple beth seder"?
- 不 - 让我试试
- No. - Here,let me try it.
呼叫麦克弗洛罗.麦克夫鲁尼路
Call mcflono mcfIlooloon
正在呼叫拉杰.库萨帕里
calling rajesh koothrappali.
真是叹为观止啊
oh,it's very impressive.
再加点种族主义
And a little racist.
你们嘲讽科技瑕疵够了吧
If we're all through playing "mock the flawed technology,"
能不能开始玩光晕了?
can we get on with halo night?
8点就该开始的 现在已经8:06
We were supposed to start at 8:00. It is now 8:06.
那就现在开始
So we'll start now.
我们得先决定
Yes,first we have to decide
这失去的6分钟要怎么补回来 削减游戏时间 厕所时间 还是吃饭时间?
if those lost six minutes will be coming out of game time, bathroom time or the pizza break.
我们可以平分成2分钟 2分钟 2分钟
We could split it two,two and two.
如果我们吃凤尾鱼披萨  厕所时间可就省不出来了
If we're having anchovies on the pizza,we can't take it out of bathroom time.
又他妈怎么了?
oh,what fresh hell is this?
嘿 佩里 请进
Oh,hey,penny. Come on in.
各位好
Hey,guys.
捡到一便士 好运行将至
See a penny,pick her up,and all the day you'll have good luck.
penny又意为便士
不 你不会
No,you won'T.
我能在这边呆会儿吗?
Uh,can I hide out here for a while?
当然可以 怎么了?
Sure. What's going on?
有个女孩 是我在内布拉斯加的老相识 她叫克里斯汀
Well,there's this girl I know from back in nebraska,christy.
她打电话给我 问起加州感觉如何
Anyway,she called me up,and she's like,"hey,how's california?"
我回答说超棒  因为不是内布拉斯加啊
And I'm like,"awesome," 'cause,you know,it's not nebraska.
然后她居然自己跑过来 要和我一起住
And the next thing I know she's invited herself out here to stay with me.
8:08咯
8:08.
她今天刚到 一直呆在我房间 唧歪每一个她在奥马哈睡过的男人
Anyway,she got here today and she's just been in my apartment yakity yakking about every guy she slept with in omaha,
差不多也就是奥马哈所有的男人
which is basically every guy in omaha,
她还在我浴室水池里 洗你能想像到的最淫荡的内衣
and washing the sluttiest collection of underwear you have ever seen in my bathroom sink.
她一次只洗一件 还是混在一起...
Is she doing it one thong at a time,or does she throw it all in...
像某种色情盛宴?
like some sort of erotic bouillabaisse?
- 他真的需要降降温 - 我知道
- He really needs to dial it down. - I know.
你不喜欢克里斯汀的话 干嘛让她留下?
So if you don't like this christy,why are you letting her stay?
她跟我弟弟睡的时候 和我表兄订婚了
Well,she was engaged to my cousin while she was sleeping with my brother,
说起来也算是个家人
so she's kind of family.
我为自己刚才的爆发道歉
I apologize for my earlier outburst.
有奥马哈骚货的民间故事可以传诵 谁还要玩光晕?
Who needs halo,when we can be regaled with the delightfully folksy tale of the whore of omaha?
我不觉得她是骚货
Oh,I don't think she's a whore.
不 她绝对是个骚货
No,yeah,she's definitely a whore.
她根本就没有原则
I mean,she has absolutely no standards.
有一次我们在...
This one time she was at...
霍华德哪去了?
where's howard?
早上好 小姐
Bonjour,mademoiselle.
我知道你是新来的
I understand you're new in town.
哦 好悲伤
Oh,good grief.
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第07集
The.Dumpling.Paradox
真不敢相信克里斯汀居然让霍华德进我家
Aw,I cannot believe christy let howard into my apartment.
我也不敢相信居然有人花钱去占星
And I cannot believe people pay for horoscopes,
更严肃的问题是 现在已经8:13 我们还没开始玩光晕
but on a more serious note, it's 8:13 and we're still not playing halo.
好吧 我们玩一对一 等他回来
Okay,fine. We'll just play one-on-one until he gets back.
一对一? 我们从不玩一对一的
One-on-one? We don't play one-on-one.
我们玩团队 不玩一对一 你这一对一
We play teams,not one-on-one. One-on-one.
现在想玩团队 只能把拉杰剖两半
Well,the only way we can play teams at this point is if we cut raj in half.
好啊 一个外国人倒下来 千百万个外国人站起来!
Oh sure,cut the foreigner in half. There's a billion more where he came from.
你们缺人的话 我加入
Hey,if you guys need a fourth,I'll play.
好主意
Great idea.
不要
No.
车轮的发明是个好主意 相对论也是个好主意
The wheel was a great idea,relativity was a great idea.
这只是个想法 还是相当糟糕的想法
This is a notion,and a rather sucky one at that.
为什么?
Why?
哦 佩里 佩里 佩里
Oh,penny,penny,penny.
哦 怎么 怎么 怎么?
Oh,what,what,what?
这是款复杂的战斗模拟 对玩家要求很高
This is a complex battle simulation with a steep learning curve.
要学习无数种武器 交通工具 和战略战术
There are myriad weapons,vehicles and strategies to master,
更别提复杂的故事背景了
not to mention an extremely intricate backstory.
好酷 我把谁的头打爆了?
oh cool. Whose head did I just blow off?
我的
Mine.
我会啦 填弹药 兄弟们
Okay,I got this. Lock and load,boys.
只有这样才能玩团队
It's the only way we can play teams.
但她缺乏经验 她搭档会被拖累
Yes,but whoever's her partner will be hamstrung by her lack of experience,
更别说她...
and not to mention the fact...
你头又掉啦
there goes your head again.
别人刚复活就宰了人家 可不符合运动精神
Okay,it's not good sportsmanship to shoot somebody who's just re-spawned.
你得给人家一个机会... 来吧!
You need to to give them a chance to... now,come on!
拉杰 拉杰! 她把我逼到死角了 掩护我!
Raj,raj! She's got me cornered.Cover me!
尝尝这个吧 还掩护呢!
Cover this,suckers!
佩里 你太火爆了!
Penny,you are on fire!
是啊 谢尔顿也着火了
Yes,and so is sheldon.
我受够了
Okay,that's it.
我不知道怎么回事 但她作弊
I don't know how,but she is cheating.
美女不可能这么会打游戏的
No one can be that attractive and this skilled at a video game.
等一下 谢尔顿 回来
Wait,wait,sheldon,come back.
你忘带东西了
You forgot something.
什么?
What?
这个血浆手榴弹
This plasma grenade.
看 在帮你灭火呢
look,it's raining you.
你就笑吧... 你会需要技术支持的
You laugh now-- you just wait until you need tech support.
唉 他就这么输不起吗?
Gosh,he's kind of a sore loser,isn't he?
公平点说 他赢了也不会开心
Well,to be fair,he's also a rather unpleasant winner.
还挺好玩的
Well,it's been fun.
佩里 我们这么合作愉快
You know,penny,we make such a good team.
也许我们可以去参加光晕锦标赛呢
Maybe we could enter a couple of halo tournaments sometime.
或者我们还是好好生活吧
Or we could just have a life.
我猜那是你的选择
I guess for you that's an option.
- 晚安 莱纳德 - 晚安
- Good night,leonard. - Good night.
和你聊天很愉快 拉杰
As usual,nice talking to you,raj.
她什么意思?
what do you suppose she meant by that?
她是个迷 拉杰
She's an enigma,raj.
还有件事... 游戏规则是佩里一位
And another thing-- there's a certain ethic to the game,penny,a well
- 有着 ... - 她走了 谢尔顿
- established... - she's gone,sheldon.
她至少该说声再见
Well,she could have said good-bye.
我有麻烦了
Okay,I have a problem.
这个叫腕骨综合症 说实话你活该
It's called carpal tunnel syndrome, and quite frankly you deserve it.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
呃 霍华德和克里斯汀好像...
Well,um,howard and christy are...
在我的卧室挺热乎的
kind of hooking up in my bedroom.
你确定?
Are you sure?
听着 我是在农场长大的
Look,I grew up on a farm,okay?
据我的经验 他们不是在做爱 就是霍华德被困在挤奶机里了
From what I heard,they're either having sex or howard's caught in a milking machine.
我能在这过夜吗?
Do you mind if I stay here tonight?
没问题 你可以睡沙发 或者我的床
No,take the couch,or my bed.
我刚换了新枕头 低过敏型
I just got new pillows. Hypo-allergenic.
我睡沙发就好
The couch is good.
暂停一下 莱纳德 过来说话
Hold that thought. Leonard,a moment.
我猜 你有点意见
Let me guess. You have a problem with this.
从何说起呢?
Where do I begin?
随你 疯人的选择
It's up to you. Crazy person's choice.
首先 我们的房间不留宿
Well,first,we don't have houseguests.
说实话 如果我付得起租金 早让你滚蛋了
Frankly,if I could afford the rent,I'd ask you to leave.
您的友谊对我意义重大 还有呢?
Your friendship means a lot to me as well. What else?
这个...
Well...
我们的地震补给啊 我们只有两人两天的储备
our earthquake supplies. We have a two-man,two-day kit.
所以呢?
So?
所以如果地震了 我们三个被困在这
So if there's an earthquake and the three of us are trapped here,
我们明天下午就没东西吃了
we could be out of food by tomorrow afternoon.
抱歉 你是说假如留佩里在这过夜 我们有可能被逼的自相残杀吗?
I'm sorry,are you suggesting that if we let penny stay we might succumb to cannibalism?
事情没发生 谁也说不准
No one ever thinks it'll happen until it does.
如你能保证不会乘睡觉时吃我们 就可以留下过夜
Penny,if you promise not to chew the flesh off our bones while we sleep,you can stay.
什么?
What?
他在玩归谬法
He's engaging in reductio ad absurdum.
逻辑学中的一种驳斥形式 用以证明矛盾的或荒谬的结论
It's the logical fallacy of extending someone's argument to ridiculous proportions
是按照前提推出的逻辑上必然的结果
and then criticizing the result.
我并不欣赏
And I do not appreciate it.
我给你拿毯子和枕头
I'll get you a blanket and a pillow.
好吧 我明显被无视 给你讲一下早晨的日程
Okay,well,since I'm obviously being ignored here,let's go over the morning schedule.
7:00到7:20 厕所归我用
I use the bathroom from 7:00 to 7:20.
因此计划一下你的清洁任务 和身体机能运作
Plan your ablutions and bodily functions accordingly.
我怎么可能计划自己的身体机能运作?
How am I supposed to plan my bodily functions?
建议你晚上11点后不要喝水
I suggest no liquids after 11:00 P.M.
放这了
Here you go.
谢谢 莱纳德
Thanks,leonard.
错了
Wrong.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
你头该朝这边
Your head goes on the other end.
为什么?
Why?
宇宙规律
It's culturally universal.
床 即使是临时的床
A bed,even a temporary bed,
都该床头朝向门口
is always oriented with the headboard away from the door.
是遵循古老的传统  防止自己被偷袭
It serves the ancient imperative of protecting oneself against marauders.
我情愿冒险
I'll risk it.
还有什么要提醒的吗?
Anything else should I know?
如果你用了我牙刷 我会从这个窗口跳下去
Yes,if you use my toothbrush, I'll jump out that window.
请别来参加我的葬礼 祝您晚安
Please don't come to my funeral. Have a good night.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
没关系
That's okay.
他的牙刷是紫外灯下树脂格子里红色的那个
Fyi-- his toothbrush is the red one in the plexiglas case under the uv light.
明白
Got it.
睡塌实
Well,sleep tight.
谢谢
Thanks.
这么说还挺好玩的 睡塌实
Funny expression,"sleep tight."
这是因为早期床的结构
It refers to the early construction of beds
床垫被绳索吊起来 所以偶尔会...
which featured a mattress suspended on interlocking ropes,which would occasionally...
睡塌实
sleep tight.
你干嘛呢?
what are you doing?
我们搬进来后每个周六早晨 我都在6:15准时醒来
Every saturday since we've lived in this apartment I have awakened at 6:15,
给自己冲一碗麦片
poured myself a bowl of cereal,
倒四分之一杯百分之二的牛奶
added a quarter cup of two percent milk,
坐在沙发的这边
sat on this end of this couch,
打开英国广播公司美国频道 看
turned on bbc america,and watched doctor who.
佩里还睡着呢
Penny's still sleeping.
我们搬进来后每个周六早晨 我都在6:15准时醒来
Every saturday since we've lived in this apartment I have awakened at 6:15,
- 给自己冲一碗麦片... - 知道了 知道了
- poured myself a bowl of cereal... - I know,I know.
你自己房间有台电视
Look,you have a tv in your room.
你为什么不来个床上早餐呢?
Why don't you just have breakfast in bed?
因为我既不是残疾 也不是庆祝母亲节的妇女
Because I am neither an invalid,nor a woman celebrating mother's day.
现在几点?
What time is it?
差不多6点半
Almost 6:30.
我睡了一整天?
I slept all day?
没有 是早上6点半
No,it's 6:30 in the morning.
你们有病吧?
What the hell is your problem?
太棒了 这碗麦片再不彼此分子独立了
Okay,this cereal has lost all its molecular integrity.
我现在有一碗麦片糊了
I now have a bowl of shredded wheat paste.
早安 我聪明的怪友们
Hola,nerd-migos.
大早上的怎么都不睡觉呢?
Why do you people hate sleep?
你穿着我的浴袍吗?
Are you wearing my robe?
是啊 抱歉 我会洗干净
Oh,yeah. Sorry,I'll have it cleaned.
没关系 你自己留着吧
That's okay,keep it.
克里斯汀呢?
Where's christy?
在洗澡
In the shower.
顺便问一句 你从哪买的丝瓜巾?
Oh,by the way,where did you get that loofah mitt?
能洗到死角哦
Yours reaches places that mine just won'T.
你用了我的丝瓜巾?
You used my loofah?
准确地说 是我俩用了
More precisely,we used your loofah.
我把她搓得欲仙欲死
I exfoliated her brains out.
这个也送给你了
You can keep that,too.
那么...我还想谈谈你的毛毛熊收藏
Well,then we'll probably need to talk about your stuffed bear collection.
霍华德?
Howard?
在这里 宝贝!
In here,milady!
我的小火车在这里
There's my little engine that could.
卡嚓 卡嚓...
Chugga-ghugga,chugga-chugga...
我再也不会看这本书了 (畅销童话: )
Well,there's one beloved children's book I'll never read again.
嗨 我是克里斯汀
Hi. Christy.
莱纳德
Leonard.
我是谢尔顿
I'm sheldon.
对 你们是霍华德的随从
Right. You're howard's entourage.
克里斯汀 你打算怎么安排?
Uh,so,christy,what are your plans?
霍华德说带我去比佛利山购物
Oh,well,howard said he'd take me shopping in beverly hills.
不是 我的意思是你的住处
Yeah,no,I meant plans to find someplace to live.
除了我这里
You know,other than with me.
我不是不欢迎你...
Not that I don't love having you,but it'S...
只是有点挤
it's a little crowded.
佩里 你想过来随时都可以啊
You know,penny,you're always welcome to stay with us.
太好了
Oh,terrific.
把这里当小旅店了
Now we're running a cute little b & B.
我作为局外人提个建议
Let me offer a little outside-the-box thinking here.
克里斯汀可以跟我住
Why doesn't christy stay with me?
首先 你住你妈家
For one thing,you live with your mother.
不是的
I do not.
是我妈住我家
My mother lives with me.
这样安排很好
Well,then it's all settled.
克里斯汀住霍华德那里 佩里回自己房间
Christy will stay with howard,penny can go back to her apartment,
我还有24分钟的可看
and I'll watch the last 24 minutes of doctor who.
不过现在只能说是 了
Although at this point,it's more like doctor why bother?
谢尔顿 你不能这么独裁...
Sheldon,you just can't dictate...
不要说话 全都走!
no more talking! Everybody go!
你怎么样?
So what do you say?
我们去沃罗威茨之家修缮一下吧?
Want to repair to casa wolowitz?
什么地方? 墨西哥快餐店?
What is that,like a mexican deli?
不好意思 之前没告诉你
I'm sorry,I should have mentioned this earlier.
我姓沃罗威茨
My last name is wolowitz.
哇 有意思
Oh,that's so cool.
我的第一个犹太人
My first jew.
我猜内布拉斯加州没多少剥玉米皮的犹太佬
I imagine there aren't very many kosher cornhuskers.
Kosher:犹太教所允许的
Cornhusker:美国内布拉斯加州居民的绰号(意为剥玉米皮的乡巴佬)
你会带我去购物吧?
But you're still taking me shopping,right?
那是当然
Anything you want.
好的 我去拿行李
Okay,I'll go pack my stuff.
待克隆人技术成熟时 我要订购一打这样的
When they perfect human cloning,I'm going to order 12 of those.
霍华德 你看不出来她在利用你吗?
Howard,can't you see she's using you?
管她呢? 昨晚她脱下睡衣 我激动得都哭了
Who cares? Last night,she pulled off her blouse and I wept.
霍华德 我了解她 懂吗?
Look,howard,I know her. Okay?
谁给她买东西 她就跟谁上床
She'll have sex with anyone,as long as they keep buying her things.
- 真的? - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
真的!
Yay!
失陪了 我要去兑换我的成人礼金券
If you'll excuse me,I have some bar mitzvah bonds to cash.
很抱歉 没有沃罗威茨我们没法吃
I'm sorry,we cannot do this without wolowitz.
没有沃罗威茨我们就不能吃中餐?
We can't order chinese food without wolowitz?
我跟你解释
Let me walk you through it.
我们是这么点的 头道蒸饺 然后左宗棠鸡
Our standard order is: The steamed dumpling appetizer,general tso's chicken,
西兰花牛柳 龙舟活鱼和素菜捞面
beef with broccoli,shrimp with lobster sauce and vegetable lo mein.
发现问题了吧
Do you see the problem?
我看到 一个问题
I see a problem.
我们整个的点菜是建立在点四只蒸饺
Our entire order is predicated on four dumplings
四道小菜、四个人分着吃的基础上的
and four entrees divided amongst four people.
那就只要三道菜好了
So,we'll just order three entrees.
好 那么舍弃哪道?
Fine. What do you want to eliminate?
多出的一个蒸饺给谁?
And who gets the extra dumpling?
可以切成三份
We could cut it into thirds.
那就不是饺子了
Then it's no longer a dumpling.
当你把它切开以后就是开口的小三明治了
Once you cut it open it is,at best,a very small open-faced sandwich.
你们好
Hi,fellas.
那个自以为会说普通话的人没来?
Oh,where's your annoying little friend who thinks he speaks mandarin?
他把自己的利益置于集体利益之前
He's putting his needs ahead of the collective good.
在这位老兄的家乡 那可是死罪
Where he comes from,that's punishable by death.
我是萨克拉门托人
I come from sacramento.
可不可以只要三个蒸饺?
Can we get an order of dumplings but with three instead of four?
不可替换
No substitutions.
这不是替换 是减量
This isn't a substitution. It's a reduction.
- 好吧 不准减量 - 行
- Okay.No reductions. - Fine.
那我们要三笼蒸饺
Uh,bring us three orders of dumplings.
一共十二个 每人四个
That's 12. We'll each have four.
可以
That works.
不行 如果吃饺子吃饱了 就要再减一道菜
No. If we fill up on dumplings,we need to eliminate another entree.
不准减菜
No eliminations.
多处来的就打包好了
If we have extra,we'll just take the leftovers home.
然后怎么分?
And divide it how?
跟你说 没沃罗威茨就是不行
I'm telling you,we cannot do this without wolowitz.
沃罗威茨和新女朋友在一起
Wolowitz is with his new girlfriend.
要不是你不让我请佩里 现在正好四个人
If you had let me invite penny,then you would have had your fourth.
你见过佩里怎么吃中国菜吗?
Have you seen penny eat chinese food?
她拿叉子吃 还把蛋卷蘸两次
She uses a fork and she double-dips her egg rolls.
我们又没点蛋卷
We don't order egg rolls.
是的 但她来了就会点蛋卷了!
Exactly,but we'd have to if she was here!
能不能快点决定?
Can we please make a decision?
不仅仅在印度有孩子在挨饿
Not only are there children starving in india,
眼前就有个印度人在挨饿
there's an indian starving right here.
要我说 不如去吃印度餐吧?
There's an idea. Why don't we just go out for indian food?
看你们几个人不错
You're nice boys.
告诉你我的办法
Tell you what I'm going to do.
我给你们上四个饺子
I'm going to bring you the four dumplings.
当我送上来的时候
When I'm walking over to the table,
也许我绊一下 碰掉一个饺子
maybe I get bumped,one of the dumplings fall to the floor.
你们什么都不知道
No one has to know.
我知道
I'll know.
汤怎么样?
how about soup?
汤总归是好分的
Yeah,we can always divide soup.
馄饨怎么分?
What about the wontons?
嗨 怎么啦?
Hey,guys,what's up?
今晚是光晕游戏之夜
It's halo night.
啊? 是啊
Yeah? Okay.
怎么?
So?
因为沃罗威茨在陪你朋友克里斯汀
Well,with wolowitz spending all of his time with your friend christy...
她不是我朋友
she's not my friend.
朋友是不会让朋友心爱的小熊全身是水的
Friends do not get their friends' care bears all sweaty.
没错 但是沃罗威茨没空
Right. Anyway,uh,with wolowitz occupied elsewhere,
我们要请你帮个忙
we had something we wanted to ask you.
- 谢尔顿? - 来了
- Sheldon? - Yes.
佩里...
penny...
我们很荣幸的邀请你
we would very much appreciate
加入我们成为光晕战队的第四名成员
it if you would be the fourth member of our halo team.
我想不说你也明白 这是多大的荣耀
I don't think I need to tell you what an honor this is.
你们真好 但是今晚我和朋友去跳舞
Oh,that's so sweet,but I'm going out dancing with a girlfriend.
你不能走 这是光晕之夜
You can't go out; it's halo night.
在佩里看来 这是跳舞之夜
Well,for penny,it's dancing night.
你每周三晚上都跳舞?
You go dancing every wednesday?
- 不 - 那就不能称跳舞之夜
No. Then that's not "dancing night."
明天陪你们玩好不好?
Look,why don't I play with you guys tomorrow?
光晕之夜在今晚
Tonight is halo night.
好像跟墙壁说话似的
It's like talking to a wall.
谢尔顿 别惹我发火
All right,now,sheldon,you and I are about to have a problem.
谢尔顿 不是早都套好了台词吗?
Sheldon,remember,we role-played this.
但是你扮的她没这么不讲理
Yes,but you didn't portray her as completely irrational.
好了 我得走了
All right,fellas,I gotta go.
祝你们好运
But good luck.
也许我们可以问她 愿不愿带我们一起去跳舞
Maybe we should've asked if we could go dancing with her and her girlfriend.
假设我们会跳舞 其实不会
Okay,assuming we could dance-- which we can't--
我们三个男生 两个女生
there are three of us and two of them.
怎么?
So?
又是中餐馆的难题
It's the chinese restaurant all over again.
我向你保证 把饺子切成三份还算简单了
I assure you that cutting a dumpling in thirds is child's play
每个人跟67%的女人跳舞才叫难
compared with three men each attempting to dance with 67% of a woman.
得了谢尔顿 快被你逼疯了!
Oh,for god's sakes,sheldon,you're driving me crazy!
你不是气我 你是气基础数学
Your anger is not with me,sir,but with basic mathematics.
不 我十分肯定就是气你
No. I'm pretty sure my anger is with you.
我们这是怎么了 分崩离析
What's happening to us? We're falling apart.
给谁打?
Who are you calling?
只有他才能给我们的宇宙带来平衡
The only man who can restore any semblance of balance to our universe.
嗨 我是霍华德 沃罗威茨
Hi,this is howard wolowitz.
我是克里斯汀 范德贝尔特
And this is christy vanderbelt.
我们不能接电话 因为在做爱!
We can't get to the phone right now because we're having sex!
你不会真把这个放在答录机上吧?
You're not going to put that on your message,are you?
不会 我说说的 等下重录
Nah,I'm just kidding. I'll re-record it.
谢尔顿 想清楚了
sheldon,think this through.
你这是让霍华德在性爱和光晕中做抉择
You're going to ask howard to choose between sex and halo.
不 是性爱和光晕3之间的抉择
No,I'm going to ask him to choose between sex and halo three.
据我所知 人类性爱还没升级到
As far as I know,sex has not been upgraded
高清晰图像以及增强版武器系统装备
to include hi-def graphics and enhanced weapon systems.
说的对 做爱有什么了不起 无非是裸体性高潮和人类接触
You're right,all sex has is nudity,orgasms and human contact.
就是说嘛
My point.
我说 能不能别在沙发上盖塑料布!
I'm just saying,you can take the damn plastic off the couch once in a while!
好方便你和霍华德叉叉?
Why,so you and howard can hump on it?
女士们 我想一定有折衷的
Ladies,ladies,I'm sure there's a middle ground.
闭嘴 霍华德
Shut up,howard!
这样吧 你们慢聊
You know what,you guys talk.
我骑车出去转一圈
I'm gonna take my scooter out for a little spin.
你开心了? 你把儿子赶出家门
You happy? You drove your own son out of the house.
你们在这里做什么?
hey,what are you guys doing here?
今天是光晕之夜
It's halo night.
他不算男人 他是傻小子
He's not a man,he's a putz!
你这个拜金女别跟我那种口气!
And don't you take that tone with me,you gold digger!
你说我什么?
What'd you call me?
你听到了
You heard me!
我跟你明说吧 你勾搭错人了
And I'll tell you something else,you're barking up the wrong tree.
只要你在 遗嘱就没他份!
'Cause as long as you're around,howard is out of the will!
知道吗? 我有更好的主意
You know what? I got better offers.
我走了
I'm outta here.
对了
that's right.
滚回巴比伦 骚货
Go back to babylon,you whore!
巴比伦常指奢华淫靡的城市
光晕之夜是吧?
So,halo night,huh?
我还以为她是从奥马哈来的
I thought she was the whore of omaha.
谢尔顿 他在你的视野里! 开火!
sheldon,you got him in your sights! Fire!
他正在给电浆枪充电!
He's charging his plasma rifle!
我不能开枪
I can't shoot now.
我隐身状态!
I'm cloaking!
拉杰! 干掉谢尔顿!
Now,raj! Kill sheldon!
我看不见他!
I can't see him!
所以这叫隐身! 死人
That's why they call it cloaking,dead man!
开始扔手榴弹!
Start throwing grenades!
扔光了!
I'm all out!
嗨 伙计们 我朋友不想跳舞了
Hey,guys. My friends and I got tired of dancing,
所以来找你们做爱
so we came over to have sex with you.
拉杰 跳进坦克里!
Raj,hop in the tank!
不是说不带坦克的吗!
We said no tanks!
地狱级没有规则!
There are no rules in hell!
该死的 血包!
Son of a bitch. Med pack!
我要血包!
I need a med pack!
跟你们说了
Told ya.
有狙击手! 用火箭筒!
There's a sniper. Use your rocket launcher!
我只有一把针刺枪! 还没子弹了
All I've got is a needler and I'm all out of ammo!
现在你连命都没了
And now you're out of life.
你干嘛按暂停?
why'd you hit pause?
我觉得...好似听到什么
I thought I heard... something.
什么?
What?
算了 不好意思 继续
No,n-never mind. Sorry.Go.